We're going to take the two primitive aortas.
Prenderemo le due aorte primitive.
In the middle, there are internal tissues, here.
Al centro, ci sono tessuti interni, qui.
Nutritive.
Nutritivo.
Do you remember what the embryo does? It grows.
Ricordate, cosa fa l'embrione? Cresce.
This is an influential reference to the neural plate,
È un riferimento che influenza la placca neurale,
which then becomes a groove.
che, a sua volta, diventa una doccia.
In this formation of a groove, it creates a trajectory.
In questa formazione di una doccia, si crea una traiettoria.
This trajectory begins to become.
Questa traiettoria inizia a diventare.
small primitive aortic ducts, and we see that the embryo
piccoli condotti aortici primitivi e si vede che l'embrione
makes a flexion movement,
fa un movimento di flessione,
of internal rotation, of adduction. A developmental movement where it returns to the center,
di rotazione interna, di adduzione. Un movimento di sviluppo in cui torna verso il centro,
simply because at some point, I have my aortas developing here and I have
semplicemente perché a un certo punto, ho le mie aorte che si sviluppano qui e ho
a telencephalization process that pulls backwards and everything moves forward.
un processo di telencefalizzazione che tira all'indietro e tutto si avvicina in avanti.
In this phase of moving forward, I initially had embryologically
In questa fase di avvicinamento in avanti, avevo inizialmente embriologicamente
two tubes that were there. These two tubes will come towards the midline and
due tubi che erano lì. Questi due tubi verranno verso la linea mediana e
at some
a un certo
point will fuse. This fusion phase, here, you
punto si fonderanno. Questa fase di fusione, qui, tu
see that through this process it
vedi che attraverso questo processo
starts to come against each other like this. Here there is still a little bit of
inizia a venire l'uno contro l'altro così. Lì c'è ancora un po' di
internal tissue,
tessuto interno,
no problem. Here there is less and less. And at some point
nessun problema. Lì ce n'è sempre meno. E a un certo punto
the two tissues here,
i due tessuti qui,
will really be against each other.
saranno davvero l'uno contro l'altro.
Since there is no more internal tissue,
Dato che non c'è più tessuto interno,
a corrosion field appears.
appare un campo di corrosione.
You have a lot of things like that happening in the body.
Avete un'enorme quantità di cose simili che accadono nel corpo.
For example, initially, I am like this,
Un esempio, all'inizio, sono così,
I have what are called branchial arches.
ho quelli che chiamiamo archi branchiali.
When I have an embryo flexion,
Quando ho una flessione dell'embrione,
we see on the outside, on the ectoderm, a sufficient amount.
si vede apparire all'esterno sull'ectoderma di suffragio.
on the inside, a compression,
nella parte interna, una compressione,
we see that with my finger,
lo vediamo con il mio dito,
and we see that it forms branchial arches.
e vediamo che forma gli archi branchiali.
At some point, here, there is a branchial arch
A un certo punto, qui, c'è un arco branchiale
that undergoes an exhausting pressure against the heart with the mandible,
che subisce contro il cuore con la mandibola
which causes an opening here, the mouth.
una pressione estenuante,
This, for example, is an example of a corrosion field.
che fa sì che si apra qui uno spazio, la bocca.
This is, for example, an example of a corrosion field.
Questo è, per esempio, un esempio di campo di corrosione.
For example, now, when we exceed
Per esempio, ora, quando superiamo
A limit, an example of a corrosion field, you are hospitalized,
Un limite, un esempio di campo di corrosione, sei ricoverato,
you are lying in your
sei sdraiato nel tuo
bed for fifteen days, three weeks, what do you start? You start
letto per quindici giorni, tre settimane, cosa inizi? Inizi
a bedsore. You have pressure, you have continuous pressure, you have the sense on the
una piaga da decubito. Hai una pressione, hai la pressione che continua, hai la sensazione al
side that is
fianco che se ne
going away and in fact you no longer have a trophic aspect. You start to have a warming first
va e in realtà non hai più un aspetto trofico. Inizi ad avere prima un riscaldamento
and then at some point you have a corrosion field and you get stuck.
e poi ad un certo punto hai un campo di corrosione e ti blocchi.
It's a new structure that appears.
È una nuova struttura che appare.
and this phenomenon
e questo fenomeno
of corrosion field
di campo di corrosione
in your system
nel tuo sistema
the development of the vascular system
lo sviluppo del sistema vascolare
you will see that it is very important
vedrete che è molto importante
it changes all the time
cambia continuamente
initially you have what is called
all'inizio hai quelle che chiamiamo
the cardinal veins
le vene cardinali
anterior
anteriori
or posterior
o meglio posteriori
then it will become subcardinal veins
poi diventeranno vene subcardinali
then supracardinal
poi supracardinali
and you will have a whole reorganization
e avrai tutta una riorganizzazione
the organization of your body based on that, based on your growth, etc.
l'organizzazione del tuo corpo in funzione di questo, in funzione della tua crescita, ecc.
These are simply fields, and then you have the spinal arteries, you have posterior vessels, etc.
Sono semplicemente campi, e poi hai le arterie spinali, hai i vasi posteriori, ecc.
Initially, you have a structure, and then through these fields of compression, decompression, etc.,
All'inizio, hai una struttura, e poi attraverso questi campi di compressione, decompressione, ecc.,
new structures appear, this is called a corrosion field.
appaiono nuove strutture, è quello che chiamiamo un campo di corrosione.
So it's like the word "destruction", I don't like it, it's a change of form.
Quindi è come la parola "distruzione", non mi piace, è un cambiamento di forma.
We're going to see the field, what we call "the loosening field", a field of art.
Vedremo il campo, quello che chiamiamo "the loosening field", un campo d'arte.
this field will explain a suction field to you. It's the same
questo campo vi spiegherà un campo di suzione. È lo stesso
pattern for all glands in the body.
schema per tutte le ghiandole del corpo.
This type of field always appears along the surfaces of epithelial tissues,
Questo tipo di campo appare sempre lungo le superfici dei tessuti epiteliali,
either of
sia di origine
ectodermal origin, or of endodermal origin. I will take an example
ectodermica, sia di origine endodermica. Prenderò un esempio
of an epithelial tissue of
di un tessuto epiteliale di tipo
endodermal type. And underneath, what do I have? I have the tissue of
endodermico. E sotto, cosa ho? Ho il tessuto di
type
tipo
Connective, in which there are vessels, in which there are small glands, in which there is
connettivo, nel quale ci sono vasi, nel quale ci sono piccole ghiandole, nel quale c'è
matrix, which has fibers, etc.
della matrice, che ha fibre, ecc.
We see appearing along the surfaces at some point, in a very first stage, a congestive phase.
Vediamo apparire lungo le superfici ad un certo punto, in un primissimo tempo, una fase
congestive.
congestizia.
As if there was an accumulation, as if it was a little water that
Come se ci fosse un accumulo, come se fosse un po' d'acqua che
came.
venait.
The image is like I'm massaging on the beach, you see.
L'image, c'est comme si je masse sur la plage, tu vois.
where the ground is a bit congested,
où  le  sol  est  un  peu  congestionné,
but when you walk on it, you feel it can sink in.
mais  quand  tu  marches  dessus,  tu  sens  qu 'il  peut  partir  dedans.
It's as if it's in the early stages, it's the initial moment.
C'est comme si c'était dans l'ébauche, c'est le moment au départ.
It's an activity, I arrive and suddenly there's quicksand.
C'est une activité, j'arrive et tout d'un coup il y a du sable mouvant.
Let's take the lung, do you remember the diaphragm being put in place?
On va prendre le poumon, vous vous souvenez de la mise en place du diaphragme.
There is a space here behind, why? Because I have my... I already have, we
Il  y  a  un  espace  ici  derrière,  pourquoi  ?  Parce  que  j 'ai  mon...  j 'ai  déjà  on
could say...
va  dire...
My digestive tube, here, like this, and behind, here, there
Mon  tube  digestif,  ici,  comme  ça,  et  derrière,  ici,  il
is, on this tissue, here, behind, just this phenomenon that happens here, a
y  a,  sur  ce  tissu,  ici,  derrière,  juste  ce  phénomène  qui  se  passe  ici,  une
fragilization, and then at some point, by the growth of the embryo, and the straightening,
fragilisation,  et  puis  à  un  moment  donné,  par  la  croissance  de  l 'embryon,  et  le  redressement,
the lengthening of my embryo, the growth here, there is a space that opens
l 'allongement  de  mon  embryon,  la  croissance  ici,  il  y  a  un  espace  qui  s 'ouvre
here, and it creates a field where the tissue
ici,  et  ça  crée  un  champ  où  le  tissu
that is there,
qui  est  là,
The epithelial is like sucked into this space.
L'épithélial est comme aspiré dans cet espace.
Do you understand what I mean? It's really like a suction cup.
Tu comprends ce que je veux dire ? C'est vraiment comme une ventouse.
I grow and I pull towards me.
Je grandis et je tire vers moi.
A suction field, I suck.
Un champ de succion, j'aspire.
The epithelial tissue, all of a sudden, descends into the connective tissue.
Le tissu épithélial, tout d'un coup, il descend dans le tissu conjonctif.
It is as if sucked into the connective tissue.
Il est comme aspiré dans le tissu conjonctif.
First phase, we see that it is...
Première phase, on voit qu'il est...
as if sucked into the tissue, which collapses into the tissue,
comme aspirer dans le tissu, qui s'effondre dans le tissu,
in a field of aspiration. It is always around the connective tissue.
dans  un  champ  d 'aspiration.  Il  est  toujours  autour  du  tissu  au  jonctif.
And there, I will find myself with two types of movements.
Et là, je vais me retrouver avec deux types de mouvements.
Either the cell descends and really creates like a gland,
Soit  la  cellule  descend  et  crée  vraiment  comme  une  blande,
like this.
comme  ceci.
And there, it will be called an exocrine gland,
Et  là,  ça  va  s 'appeler  une  glande  exocrine,
the cells will secrete a substance that will be put into the lumen
les  cellules  vont  secréter  une  substance  qui  va  être  mis  dans  la  lumière
which is created by here the tube, for example the
qui  est  créée  par  ici  le  tube,  par  exemple  la
gallbladder, an exocrine type gland, or
vésicule  biliaire,  une  glande  de  type  exocrine,  ou
if it goes further into the metabolic field, it will create what is called
si  ça  va  plus  loin  dans  le  champ  métabolique,  ça  va  créer  ce  qu 'on  appelle
an exocrine gland.
une  glande  exocrine.
here it disappears, and there is just a gland right in the middle here, it
ici  ça  disparaît,  et  il  reste  juste  une  glande  en  plein  milieu  ici,  ça
will be called an endocrine gland,
va  s 'appeler  une  glande  endocrine,
that means it will secrete the substance outside.
ça veut dire qu'elle va secréter la substance à l'extérieur.
And what is there? There is my whole vascular network, I will take that
Et  qu 'est -ce  qu 'il  y  a  là  ?  Il  y  a  tout  mon  réseau  vesculaire,  je  vais  prendre  ça
in the blood.
dans  le  sang.
On the lung it remains, on the liver it remains,
Sur le poumon ça reste, sur le foie ça reste,
But under the pancreas, you have two pancreases, you have the exocrine pancreas and the endocrine pancreas,
Mais  sous  le  pancréas,  vous  avez  deux  pancréas,  vous  avez  le  pancréas  exocrine  et  le  pancréas  endocrine,
it is a metabolic field that developed in a field of aspiration that occurred at the same
è un campo metabolico che si è sviluppato in un campo di aspirazione che si è formato nello stesso
time, but the image is that some went further here, they lost
momento, ma l'immagine è che alcuni sono andati oltre qui, hanno perso
their correspondence, they became simple small islets of
la loro corrispondenza, sono diventati semplici piccole isole di
small glands inside the system, which produce another metabolic plan
piccole brughiere all'interno del sistema, che producono un altro piano metabolico
of aminocritic type.
di tipo aminocritico.
whereas the zones, it is a gland that will produce the insulin system, for example.
mentre le zone, è una ghiandola che produrrà il sistema di
insulin, for example.
l'insulina per esempio.
The lungs, you have to consider them as a gland, it's a respiratory gland.
I polmoni, dobbiamo considerarli come una ghiandola, è una ghiandola respiratoria.
It's the same developmental algorithm, but in different spaces
È lo stesso algoritmo di sviluppo, ma in spazi
and in a different chronology.
e in una cronologia diversa.
It's a negative question at the pulmonary level.
È una questione negativa a livello polmonare.
which is maintained by the system.
che è mantenuto dal sistema.
If I cut the breach of the parietal system,
Se taglio la breccia del sistema parietale,
the lung returns to its original form.
il polmone, torna alla sua forma iniziale.
That's why we create the vacuum.
È per questo che creiamo il vuoto.
And in fact, these are aspiration mechanisms, it's vacuum.
E in realtà, sono meccanismi di aspirazione, è il vuoto.
Which maintains, you see.
Che mantiene, vedi.
It's not a difference in metabolic field,
Non è una differenza di campo metabolico,
it's a difference in growth.
è una differenza di crescita.
So it's the same field, but it includes the same field.
Quindi è lo stesso campo, ma comprende lo stesso campo.
One of them goes, it's a bit stronger and it loses its connectivity.
Ce n'è uno che va, è un po' più forte e perde la sua connettività.
it's
è
all organs
tutti gli organi
which are of epithelial origin
che sono di origine epiteliale
but life at the beginning
ma la vita all'inizio
it's like a big suction field
è come un grande campo di aspirazione
the environment and the epigenetics
l'ambiente e la ricongenerazione
at the beginning
all'inizio
you have the environment
hai l'ambiente
and on the tissue
e sul tessuto
you have activities
hai delle attività
you have a lot of molecules
hai un sacco di molecole
that will release morphogens
che rilasceranno morfogeni
which will greatly
che andranno enormemente
But what is the environment to the electric field, what is the environment and what is the environment
Ma qual è l'ambiente al campo elettrico, qual è l'ambiente e qual è l'ambiente
to your article's map?
alla tua mappa dell'articolo?
So there, we saw, for example, the first metabolic field, it was how it will
Quindi lì, abbiamo visto, per esempio, il primo campo metabolico, era come questo
organize corrosion fields to create new structures.
organizzare campi di corrosione per creare nuove strutture.
And the extreme case of a corrosion field is a bedsore, but there, it is
E il caso estremo di un campo di corrosione, è un'ulcera, ma lì, è
a destruction, but it is a destruction of the internal tissue.
una distruzione, ma è una distruzione del tessuto interno.
That's why...
È per questo che...
on the other side, it was also a destruction
dall'altra parte, era anche una distruzione
of the internal tissue, but with the appearance
del tessuto interno, ma con l'apparizione
of a new structure.
di una nuova struttura.
Whereas in the bedsore,
Mentre nella cicatrice,
it's just the internal tissue
è solo il tessuto interno
that is damaged.
che è danneggiato.
Through this process,
Attraverso questo processo,
we begin to perceive
si inizia a percepire
how in the developing embryo
come nell'embrione che si sta costruendo
will appear,
apparirà,
depending on your genome,
in funzione del vostro genoma,
depending on space and time,
in funzione dello spazio e del tempo,
different metabolic fields
dei diversi campi metabolici
that will begin to participate in this creation.
che inizieranno a partecipare a questa creazione.
We each have a metabolic field.
Ognuno di noi ha un campo metabolico.
And if I go too far in a system,
E se io vado troppo oltre in un sistema,
I will disrupt that whole field.
disturberò tutto quel campo.
That's the idea of homeostatic guarantee.
Questa è l'idea della garanzia omeostatica.
Everyone must at some point reach their state of equilibrium.
Ognuno deve ad un certo punto raggiungere il suo stato di equilibrio.
This is a dilation field.
Questo è un campo di dilatazione.
We are in a structure that is being built.
Siamo in una struttura che si sta costruendo.
I have a tissue type, at some point,
Ho un tessuto di un certo tipo, ad un certo punto,
a mesoblastic tissue
un tessuto mesoblastico
So, we have a field here, of our unities.
Quindi, abbiamo un campo qui, delle nostre unità.
On another plane, we can have a dilation field.
Su un altro piano, possiamo avere un campo di dilatazione.
I am in dilation.
Sono in dilatazione.
if it is continuous, it will give a field
se è continuo, darà un campo
of retention.
di ritenzione.
So, these are all the muscles,
Allora, questi sono tutti i muscoli,
these are all the ligaments, all the fascia.
questi sono tutti i legamenti, tutte le fasce.
This, this gives all the bones.
Questo, questo dà tutte le ossa.
And this is another way
E questa è un'altra maniera
for the bone to appear. Because you have seen
per l'osso di apparire. Perché avete visto
in the bone,
nell'osso,
we saw that there was membranous bone
abbiamo visto che c'era l'osso membranoso
and cartilaginous bone.
e l'osso cartilagineo.
So it all depends on whether it will undergo a field
Allora tutto dipende se subirà un campo
of compression
di compressione
or decompression in its formation.
o di decompressione nella sua formazione.
The vault is a tissue that...
La volta, è un tessuto che...
is made by growing.
si forma crescendo.
The base is a tissue that is made by compression.
La base, è un tessuto che si forma in compressione.
And there, we add another metabolic field
E qui, aggiungiamo un altro campo metabolico
which we call contusion fields
che chiamiamo campi di contusione
or distusion fields.
o campi di distusione.
In other words, these fields,
In altre parole, questi campi,
these are fields, either because the cells are compressed,
sono campi, sia perché le cellule sono compresse,
that will give cartilaginous tissues,
questo darà i tessuti cartilaginei,
but it's also the whole mechanism,
ma è anche tutto il meccanismo,
the whole establishment of a metabolic tissue.
tutta la messa in atto di un tessuto metabolico.
of a metabolic growth movement,
di un movimento di crescita metabolica,
the contusion field and the distusion field.
il campo di contusione e il campo di distensione.
Here, it will give different types of tissues.
Qui, questo darà diversi tipi di tessuti.
So there, we have a somewhat global image
Quindi, qui abbiamo un'immagine globale
that must be seen in the growth of development,
che dobbiamo vedere nella crescita dello sviluppo,
where each tissue will reach an equilibrium
dove ogni tessuto raggiungerà un equilibrio
according to its destiny and its bodily situation, its genome and its environment
in funzione del suo destino e della sua situazione corporea, del suo genoma e del suo ambiente
in its growth force,
nella sua forza di crescita,
each one will at some point maintain itself, as I told you.
ognuno a un certo punto si manterrà, come vi ho detto.
If we go too far, normally I would have a tendon here,
Se andiamo troppo oltre, normalmente qui avrei un
and then if I go too far, it will become calcifying tendinitis.
tendine, e poi se vado troppo oltre, diventerà una tendinite calcificante.
So I go from a retention field towards something denser.
Quindi parto da un campo di ritenzione verso qualcosa di più denso.
I lose metabolic qualities at the tissue level.
perdo qualità di ordine metabolico a livello tissutale.
Okay? Do you understand?
Ok? Capite?
And that's our role, it's to globally maintain this homeostatic principle
Ed è lì che il nostro ruolo è mantenere globalmente questo
homeostatic principle
principio omeostatico
through these primitive embryonic fields that organize this process
attraverso questi campi embrionali primitivi che organizzano questo processo
and which maintain.
e che mantengono.
This is where all this embryonic force makes sense.
È qui che tutta questa forza embrionale acquista senso.
Which is always there, which is a guarantor of this...
Che è sempre lì, che è una garanzia di questa...
homeostasis because it reached at some point
omeostasi perché ha raggiunto a un certo punto
an equilibrium.
un equilibrio.
This is where this great balancing act takes place
È lì, è questo grande gioco di equilibrio che si crea
with always this reference
con sempre questo riferimento
to maintain
per mantenere
its power.
la sua potenza.
It's a big field here.
È un grande campo qui.
You have the liver, you have a stomach, you are each
Tu hai il fegato, tu hai uno stomaco, siete ciascuno
an equilibrium. Everything is fine.
un equilibrio. Va tutto bene.
You are in harmony,
Siete in armonia,
in homeostatic equilibrium
in equilibrio omeostatico
in relation to the system. One of them starts
rispetto al sistema. Ce n'è uno che inizia
to mess up. One of them starts
a sballare. Ce n'è uno che inizia
to eat badly.
a mangiare male.
He starts eating junk, stuff, he changes his metabolism.
Inizia a mangiare schifezze, cose, cambia il suo metabolismo.
What do the tissues do? They will respond differently.
I tessuti, cosa fanno? Risponderanno in modo diverso.
And all of a sudden, I get hepatomegaly, damn it, I have less blood flowing, I get
E all'improvviso, mi viene un'epatomegalia, cavolo, ho meno sangue che passa, mi viene
hypertension.
un'ipertensione.
I get hypertension, my nervous system starts to mess up.
Mi viene un'ipertensione, il mio sistema nervoso inizia a sballare.
And you start to go, and on top of that, what will the tissues do?
E tu inizi a partire, e su questo, i tessuti, cosa faranno?
They will first try to maintain themselves, oh, what's happening? We need to change a bit.
Prima cercheranno di mantenersi, oh, cosa succede? Dobbiamo cambiare un po'.
We needed a bit of tendinitis there.
Ci voleva un po' di tendinite, lì.
In a bench, huh.
In una panca, eh.
we're going to tell him to calm down
diremo che si calmerÃ
then the heart
poi il cuore
starts to degrade
inizia a degradarsi
then the body wants to reject
poi il corpo vuole rigettare
at the beginning it will do because you have different
all'inizio lo farÃ  perché hai diversi
magnets than you, it will use
magneti che tu, userÃ
different things, first
diverse cose, prima
it will try to get the disease out
cercherÃ  di far uscire la malattia
then if it doesn't succeed it will do
poi se non ci riesce farÃ
until at some point, it makes neoformations
fino a un certo punto, fa delle neoformazioni
these are all substrates
sono tutti substrati
so we have to try to find
quindi bisogna cercare di ritrovare
the layers in which we can be
gli strati in cui possiamo essere
and help the person to...
e aiutare la persona a...
to change again. And we had seen
a cambiare di nuovo. E avevamo visto
that at the base, it was the first
che alla base, era il primo
course, practically the first slide
corso, praticamente la prima diapositiva
important, the chronology of appearance
importante, la cronologia di apparizione
of communication systems.
dei sistemi di comunicazione.
I very often invite people,
Io, molto spesso invito le persone,
all my patients will leave, and they will want
tutti i miei pazienti, usciranno, e avranno voglia
at least to try meditation.
in ogni caso di provare la meditazione.
I try to bring them
Cerco di portarli
towards themselves,
verso se stessi,
to self-synchronize them,
di auto-cronizzarli,
self-synchronize,
auto-cronizzare,
did you say that?
hai detto questo?
Imagine, I have cells that...
Immagina, ho delle cellule che...
There are two cells pushing against each other.
Ci sono due cellule che si spingono l'una contro l'altra.
There is a mitosis happening.
C'è una mitosi che si verifica.
It's a contusion field.
È un campo di contusione.
But at some point, a contusion field, it pushes, it will laterally create a dissolution field.
Ma a un certo punto, un campo di contusione, spinge, creerÃ  lateralmente un campo di
dissolution.
dissoluzione.
So it's actually simply, you just have to remember for one, one makes cartilaginous tissues
Quindi in realtÃ  semplicemente, devi solo ricordare per uno, uno fa tessuti cartilaginei
young, the other makes cartilaginous tissues after the young ones.
giovani, l'altro fa tessuti cartilaginei dopo i giovani.
Dissolution will engender a corrosion field or which will engender...
La dissoluzione genererÃ  un campo di corrosione o che genererÃ ...
an oxysion field, everything self-balances.
un campo di ossidazione, tutto si auto-equilibra.
But don't worry,
Ma non preoccupatevi,
next time, I'm going to start
la prossima volta, inizierò
to do this, and when I develop,
a fare questo, e quando sviluppo,
I add all the fields. And there, we start
aggiungo tutti i campi. E lì, iniziamo
to suddenly have a kind of
ad avere improvvisamente una specie di
movement of fields.
movimento dei campi.
Because this is just seen on a tissue level.
Perché questo è visto solo a livello tissutale.
After, you have
Dopo, avete
the whole organization
tutta l'organizzazione
cellular, then you have the whole organization
cellulare, poi avete tutta l'organizzazione
molecular, then you have
molecolare, poi avete
the whole meosthetic, atomic organization,
tutta l'organizzazione meostesica, atomica,
subatomic, and you
subatomica, e voi
really remember this phrase
ricordatevi davvero questa frase:
the sacrum is the basis of cortical development
il sacro è alla base dello sviluppo corticale.
if the sacrum is free
Se il sacro è libero,
the vertebral axis is free
l'asse vertebrale è libero.
if the vertebral axis is free
Se l'asse vertebrale è libero,
the medullary aspect is free
l'aspetto midollare è libero.
if the medullary level is free
Se il livello midollare è libero,
the cranium is free
il cranio è libero.
the sacrum is something I check
Il sacro è qualcosa che verifico
every time anyway
ogni volta, in ogni caso.
clear sacrum point
Punto sacro liberato,
any way
in qualsiasi modo
you do it
tu lo faccia,
the sacrum must
è necessario che il sacro
all the synchronicities
tutte le sincronicità,
this is an important synchronicity
questa è una sincronicità importante,
here already with the peritoneum
qui già con il peritoneo.
so the neural tube is an articulation
Quindi il tubo neurale è un'articolazione
with the cavity
con la cavità
cardio-peritoneal
cardio-peritoneale.
and we can even say that
E possiamo anche dire che
the urogenital axis
l'asse urogenitale,
by its level of creation
per il suo livello di creazione,
by its mesodermal force
per la sua forza mesodermica
of development is the articulation
di sviluppo, è l'articolazione
between the two
tra i due.
the meso is the articulation between the endo and the ecto
Il meso è l'articolazione tra l'endo e l'ecto,
because there we have to forbid
perché qui bisogna vietare
the entire vascular system to truly understand this diagram.
tutto il sistema vascolare per avere veramente la comprensione di questo schema.
It's the importance of the brain with the liver, with the heart, with the lungs, with
Questa è l'importanza del cervello con il fegato, con il cuore, con i polmoni, con
the plexus
il plesso
or the enteric and with the renal system. We develop, it interferes in the
o gli enterici e con il sistema renale. Si sviluppa, questo interferisce nel
functioning.
funzionamento.
It's the micro-time, that's a bit later. These are the synchronicities and that's
Questo è il micro-tempo, questo è un po' più tardi. Queste sono le sincronicità e questo è
later too, not now.
anche più tardi, non è adesso.